we're going to do one more meditation
second you ready
you wanna hear my stomach making noise I
[Music]
recorded with Amazon I recorded some of
myself and they you go to a special room
it's on Springs and there's a window and
the guy sits with the book and you sit
with the book and he stares at you and
if you say the slightest thing wrong he
says stop start again and then this guy
came in with a big color a lady actually
and she she says I'm ready for you and
I'm like what
and she tied it on my stomach and she
said we always tie a pillow on your
stomach when you're recording an auto
audio book because your stomach makes
noise so if you put the iPhone here you
can get the fall
Geshe Michael
here we go relax your eyelids relax your
mouth
shoulders are maybe still a little bit
tight check check your shoulders
especially if you did work class
yesterday
just slightly tense your stomach
this meditation which is number 11 I
think in this one we do the opposite
from what we did last time so I'd like
you to go back in your life even very
far when you were a very young and what
are the seeds that you are most proud of
when did you do the really kind things
for someone else took care of someone
who was very sick or served poor like
our New York sangar doing what are the
moments when you really sacrifice what
you wanted and serve someone else take a
few minutes and think about the
highlights of your spiritual life
now again please think about small baby
steps you are taking in nowadays to
achieve your goals or solve your
problems by using seeds for steps to
plant good seeds and the four powers to
stop old ones think about the progress
you're making the evolution in this new
view of what makes things work
right
you
and then finally draw this connection
again and those good things you did many
of them were long before you really
understood about seeds though those old
good seeds are waiting in your mind to
grow and they are watered they are woken
up by all the attempts you make nowadays
to use the four steps to use seeds which
is taking refuge so try to appreciate
and draw mental connections between the
attempts you are making nowadays to
plant seeds and the very huge old good
seeds that you planted which have been
multiplying ever since then and if you
can in your through the in between and
in your meditations if you can
strengthen that mental connection
between your practices nowadays a good
seed you plug that long ago that have
been building up lots of interest then
it will trigger those season and cause
them to your flower in your life in the
coming weeks and months and you'll see a
very sharp increase in beautiful things
in your life so draw that connection
and then try to imagine how those seats
might open if you animal helped someone
financially try to imagine how your life
will become very stable and you'll have
enough to do the things you want to do
to help other people and if it was that
you serve someone who was elderly or
sick you can look forward to some very
good health strong health for many years
and if it's not yourself someone with
their relationship that you can look
forward to a very beautiful relationship
with your partner your family friends
because you tribute them you ordered
them by taking refuge and using these
principles of seeds and refusing to do
things that don't really work
three deep exhale
I mean you can slowly open take a
stretch